deconet.com 2010-03-05

# Using Deconet

Deconet AB ("Deconet") is committed to protecting your privacy. Deconet respects the privacy of its customers and keeps all personal data strictly confidential. This Privacy Policy explains what data that is collected by Deconet and how that data is processed and used. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  

By using Deconet you expressively consent to Deconet's use and disclosure of your personal data in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to the use and disclosure described below please do not use any of Deconet's services.  

Deconet has established the following rules regarding the processing and use of personal data.  

### **Processing of Personal Data**  

Deconet collects, registers, stores and uses your personal data to allow you to sell or purchase items through Deconet's website ([www.deconet.com](http://www.deconet.com/)). Deconet also maintains such data in order to provide you with a safe, efficient, and personalized experience and to keep you informed about new developments at Deconet unless you have indicated that you do not wish to receive such information.   

For the most part you can search anonymously on Deconet's website. However, some of Deconet's online services require that you provide Deconet with personal data such as your name, address and credit/debit card information when you wish to pay with debit or credit card. Under certain circumstances Deconet may require additional financial information. Deconet has the right and possibility to verify the stated information and investigate an individual's use of credit/debit card.   

The information is used for order processing but can also be used for internal data processing, such as the tracking and reviewing of search statistics collected when you visit Deconet's website. As an additional service, Deconet may also use this information to personalize the website to suit your requirements. You always have the option not to provide personal data and other information by choosing to not use a particular service or feature.   

In order to participate as a vendor on Deconet's website, you must open a Showroom by agreeing to the Terms & Conditions, completing the Showroom Membership Application, and agreeing to the Showroom Agreement. During the registration process you will be required to give Deconet personal data, including but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and billing information.   

### **E-mail**  

In order to offer you advance information about new listings and other services, Deconet will send you e-mails based on the information you voluntarily have provided and your earlier use of Deconet's website. Deconet tracks and reviews some of the information you have accessed on the website in order to provide you with these services.   

Deconet's newsletter allows you to choose to cancel Deconet's newsletter service at any time. You may also send Deconet an e-mail at: [unsubscribe@deconet.com](mailto:unsubscribe@deconet.com) at any time to have your e-mail address removed from Deconet's mailing list.   

### **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

_Aggregate Information_ (non-personally identifiable): Deconet may share information that is not personal data with its partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users and individual users will never be linked to such information.   

_Personal Data:_ Deconet will never sell personal data to any third party and will never share any personal data except for in the manner detailed in the Exceptions section or otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.   

_Log files:_ As with most other web sites, Deconet automatically collects and stores certain information on a regular basis. This information includes, but is not limited to, Internet protocol ("IP") addresses, web browser information, Internet service provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click data. This information is used to analyze trends, to administer the website, and to gather demographic information about the user base as a whole. It is not personal data, nor is it linked to personal data.   

_Cookies:_ Deconet uses cookies - a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive to identify your browser's software to the websites you visit. Cookies allows Deconet to recognize you, track your visits to Deconet's website as well as register your language preference for your next visit to Deconet's website, helping Deconet to provide a more personalized and enhanced experience for customers visiting the website.   

_Deconet Forum:_ Any information you disclose during your use of the Deconet Forum may be read, collected, or used by other Deconet visitors who have access to the forum. Therefore, Deconet cannot be held responsible for any personal data you choose to submit to the forum for viewing by other users. If Deconet becomes aware of abuse of the Deconet forum, Deconet reserves the right to take further action, including but not limited to, suspending/canceling a user or Seller account and/or other legal action.   

_Intellectual Property Rights:_ Any images, text or other data submitted by a user on Deconet, Decopedia or any of its associated sites shall be free to collect and use by Deconet for any purpose without any limitations in scope or time. The user certifies that there are no restrictions related to the usage of the images, text or data that he submits, and that the images, text and data are not in conflict with any intellectual property rights, including but not limited to trademark and copyright.   

_External Service Providers:_ Deconet may work with external service providers when performing services to you in connection with the website (e.g. shipping and payment services). If you choose to use Deconet's services and, in the course of doing so, disclose personal data and other information to the external service provider, their use of your information may be governed by their respectively privacy policy.   

_Transfer outside EU and EEA:_ You understand and agree that any personal data provided by you when using the website and communicating with Deconet, for the legitimate purposes set out herein, may be transferred to a country outside of the EU or EEA (including, but not limited to, Switzerland and the United States of America), even if such country does not provide an adequate level of data protection in accordance with the requirements of the EU Directive on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (95/46/EC).   

Please note that your personal data may be stored and processed on computers outside of Sweden, in countries which might have regulations less stringent than Swedish laws. Deconet will hold and transmit your data in a safe, confidential and secure environment. Deconet cannot, however, ensure that all of your communications with Deconet and other personal data will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.  

### **Access to and Deregistration of Personal Data**

If any of your personal data changes or is wrong or if you no longer desire registration and access to Deconet, you may edit/delete your data through the [My Deconet page].   

If you want to deregister from the website Deconet will, upon your written request, deactivate your account, contact information and financial information from Deconet's active databases. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with Deconet's deactivation policy and applicable law. Deconet will retain in its files data you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce any agreement with you or keep Deconet's feedback system in place. Further, such prior data is never completely removed from Deconet's databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back-up" systems. If you ask for deregistration, you will no longer be able to use the services that require personal data.   

### **Security**  

All personal data is maintained in a secure database at Deconet and is kept strictly confidential. Access to your personal data is strictly limited to authorized employees of Deconet.   

Deconet has established administrative regulations to ensure that employee access to the personal data maintained on any Deconet server is strictly controlled and limited only to necessary use.   

All Deconet's servers containing personal data are protected against unauthorized physical and electronic access. This protection consists of an electronic firewall as well as additional security systems featuring virus scanning, security system installation, vulnerability testing, backup and server recovery, employee training, security control and other measures designed to improve data security on an ongoing basis.   

### **Credit card payments**  

Deconet uses approved transfer and storage protocols on its website to handle confidential information such as credit card and bank information in compliance with the PCI DSS standard. In addition to that, all credit card information and payments are 3D Secure compliant.   

These protocols, such as encryption, ensure that only authorized persons at the credit card company (the card acquirer) can access your personal data. Therefore all credit card and bank information is encrypted before being securely transmitted over the Internet to the credit card company (the card acquirer).   

### **Sale or Merger**  

Should Deconet undergo a business transition, merger, sale, or acquisition by another entity, your personal data will likely be among the assets that are transferred. Should this situation arise, Deconet will notify you by prominently placing a notice on this website.   

### **Exceptions**  

If there is a court order, an order from a public authority, the police or a legal authority, Deconet can be obliged to disclose your personal data.   

### **Changes**  

Deconet reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy when necessary and will notify you regarding significant changes to this Privacy Policy by prominently placing a notice on this website.   

### **Contact Deconet**  

Deconet AB, a Swedish limited liability company (reg.no 556758-3843), is the controller of the personal data collected via Deconet's website. Deconet will process any personal data in compliance with the Swedish Data Protection Act (1998:204). If you have any questions regarding Deconet's processing of your personal data or wishes information concerning the purpose of the processing or this Privacy Policy, please contact Deconet on the address or phone number set out below. You may also contact Deconet if you detect errors in your personal data or believe that Deconet has processed your personal data in conflict with applicable regulations or this Privacy Policy. Deconet will then rectify, block and/or erase such erroneous personal data and rectify the processing accordingly.   

Adress: Grev Turegatan 19, 114 38 Stockholm, Sweden

Deconet AB 2009. All rights reserved. Use of this site signifies your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions.
